[{"answer": "Well, I think all of us have been captivated about -- talking about Michael and Ryan, and there's the rest of the world that has a lot talent.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "But this French swimmer Yannick Agnel has really taken the scruff of the neck of the swimming competition and changed the whole game, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "There's so much money in this.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Should Phelps have basically quilt after Beijing on the ultimate high?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't want to speculate on anything that would be negative to her performance.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I think that they're in sort of a quandary about this because they actually bid for the Olympic Games a number of years ago and paid the International Olympic Committee billions of dollars.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Given social media now as it is, do you think it's time that NBC bit the bullet and began to broadcast the big stuff live?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "He gave me his flowers.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What was the first thing he said to you afterwards?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "No, I've only seen him from far away.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Oh you haven't?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "I've always been honest with all my kids.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "It's about being honest, tough love?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "They have to be a family loving person that could stand having a large family and crazy family at that.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Who would be the right kind of woman for your boy?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "OCHTE: Yes.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "That apparently he cries at movies and stuff like that, is that right?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Yes, he's very caring and loves kids.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "So that makes him instantly more lovable to women, isn't it?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "It's Ryan.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "What did you make of it as his mother?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "You prefer him not to, would you?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Yes, but we call all our family and we tell them how they did immediately.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Are they anxious to see it in real time on television?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "I think sports has to be live, doesn't it, it on TV?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, I feel all right.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "So how are you feeling?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "No, not yet.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Tired?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, you also warned me, you've been answering questions all day.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "You get that, right?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I mean, sometimes I feel it, but, I mean, I like to just think of myself as a normal person who just has a passion, has a goal and a dream and goes out and does it.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "And what do you feel about that responsibility?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Well, not spending 20 years in the pool.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What do you consider normal?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Do you know anybody else that has done that?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I mean, if you want to be the best, you have to do things that other people aren't willing to do.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What is the motivation at the end of the day for that kind of extreme dedication?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Olympic gold medalist.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "What were the young Michael Phelps dreams?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I mean, I grew up.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "From what age did you know that?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I would always try to.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "When you're at home playing, do you play board games together?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Michael Jordan.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "Who are your sporting idols?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "He changed the sport of basketball in my eyes.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Why him?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I haven't.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Have you met him?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I've -- you know, I've had that thought a lot.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "What would you ask him if you were able to meet Michael Jordan?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I mean I think part of me would ask him about what made him come back to the sport.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "What's the thing you're most curious about with him?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "You know I'm sure I'll be the first one to admit I've made a lot of mistakes in my life.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "How have you dealt with that side of things?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Not too good.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "When you knew that picture was coming out, how did you feel?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Like the worst in the world, you know, like I lost all the -- I mean, I think it sort of just -- yes, it's terrible.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "I mean, did you feel -- what is that feeling like?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "You know I think -- my mom has always been obviously how all moms are.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "How did you brace yourself for that?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Yes, I did, yes.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Do you feel people overreacting?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I think the biggest thing is you got to find who's real and who's not.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Have you found you've got more attractive the more gold medals you won?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I was assuming a woman.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "With what?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Sure definitely probably, high school.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Have you had your heart broken?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I mean, I think they're both learning experiences.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "A race you really wanted to win?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "For me it's more about personal goals and things I want to achieve myself.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Does winning that gold medal repeatedly come above everything else?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "That will be it?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Probably going to need to do something for exercise.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Will you still swim a lot for fun?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Is swimming still fun for you?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I think one of the biggest things after I do retire is, you know, now when I go to the ocean, go to the beach, I don't want get in the water.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "You could imagine just doing laps for no reason?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "I mean, the biggest thing is -- I talk about how I got to where I am, a dream, a plan and I reach for it.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "What have you found makes or can make a difference?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "There are things that are protected, yes.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Do you protect it?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What was going through your mind through that period?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "I mean, I wouldn't say it was as motivated as I've ever been.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Do you feel now as motivated as you've ever been?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Sixteen.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "How many medals, do you know how many you've won?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "A bit of doubt about this, you actually know where they are?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Being the first Michael Phelps that's really the only thing.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "How would you like to be remembered whatever happens in London?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Enormously.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "First of all, are you enjoying the games?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "In fact, what I heard from Mitt Romney and it was great to see it said so clearly.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "So what do you make of that?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I think it's long been the policy of our country to ultimately have our embassy in the nation's capital of Jerusalem.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "If you become president of the United States, would you move the U.S. embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I think it's absolutely true.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Is that your view?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "We were disappointed.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Were you disappointed with that?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "I'm 33.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "How old are you for goodness sakes?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Does it get any less exciting, less enjoyable?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's such an honor.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "How do you feel representing America and doing so for such a long period of time?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Well, you know, obviously, my heart goes out for the victims and their families and it's really sad this even occurred.", "docId": "120730pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "As someone as a professional marksman, what do you think about the whole debate that's raging about gun control and so on?", "qSentId": 627}]